Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in...
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Flow
Hearts in the balance
Every card an open door
Feel the romance
In every arcane lore
Hi, guys. Hi, KZ. Hi, Ilya, Ilja. Hi, Yvonne McDonald. Hi, Samantha.
Hello, everybody. How are you guys? You guys hearing me okay? I'm using my new headphones.
Sometimes I got mixed reviews on them, but hopefully they sound okay.
I'm just having a look at what's going on. And so, yeah, it's been an interesting day.
I had an interesting time last night, let me see.
Oh, let's check out our messages.
Let's check out our messages.
I'm welcome to everybody.
Okay, hi, hey guys.
So, you know, I was on last night
and then I just wasn't feeling it
because I was like Tommy James
and somebody else were here
just like every little thing.
I said, hey, what are you?
Right, wireless headphones just sound different.
Yeah, these are always sound good.
Yeah, thank you.
These were, these are actually like noise canceling.
And they're like they're like 20 bucks
Which is pretty awesome because they have like you know bows. I've had the bows ones too. They're like $300 and it's like
What is like really the difference between a $300 to the headphones and at $20 to the headphones these days? We're probably not like
Terribly too much. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no spirit
Spirit should not be saying that in the first place. I mean, it's like you're not you don't say that but then
I have to go in
I'll kick him out myself
That's not good spirit. No spirit be kind
Okay, so yeah, but it was interesting like last night I see now for a little bit then I got to shopping a little bit
You know, I'm kind of like, you know, who thought it now
But the thing that she moved is that it's like
Like everything is like you always win everything's like a win. It's like, oh you here you go
But then it's like if you look at the little things it says it's just fake
It says it's like, oh everyone will get the best result. It's like, you know, it's just basically a
Something to like, you know, excite people you have to read the fine print
But then you have some cool stuff like
So what did I get? I got some t-shirts. Maybe I don't know if I got them there. Oh, yeah
I did get it something called the cabal a cabala deck of cards, you know as the Hebrew letters and different like, you know
cabala
correspondences
I mean it's like stuff. I mean, yeah, it's basically stuff. There's stuff from China
There's stuff in the you know sitting from China in the warehouses, right?
This is Alexander's underwear and
I think Alex and I would like to vote for your
Hey, what's up? Halo?
So anyways, I take boys, right? So what else?
Yeah, but then it's like her to say oh saying oh, you know you know you
Keep saying I have a deal and it's like everything's free. I
order that
everything has cost me
the normal price
is cheap but
Hey guys, so I mean the jewelry is really cheap a dollar eight. There's like that piece of jewelry
That's like over two dollars that you know a lot of stuff is actually like really
really
You know kind of jump like a lot of stuff in this world, right?
I think there's actually a very few things that are like actually
It's a precious metal and they do precious like rare something every like a lot of stuff is just like crap, you know
And we worry about all this stuff, you know, some of that's cool stuff
But anyway, I'm getting I'm three pairs of glasses. Look at these nails goldfish press on nails. Look at this now. Interesting. Oh
This is right now
Yeah, I have a, you know, I have a show on TikTok too.
I don't know if the person's watching this show, but hello.
I'm responding.
I just started on...
Okay, it's great helping people.
Also, I found like a few of the little programs that are kind of like helping me with like
Like there's a program on my phone. It's called TubeBuddy, and I just it looks like you know
It's interesting website, okay, so it's basically I'm on a trial for it. Let me see if I can find it TubeBuddy if I can
See it in here because it does tell you interesting information
I think about my show and stuff
I mean, I have everything on members only.
I'll tell you how many people disliked my show.
It's shocking news, guys.
OK, so here, I'll show you.
So you can see I have 2,026 subscribers.
And then it goes over.
Like the engagement like so yesterday's it was 20% engagement like one fifth of the chat engaged
You know and so usually it's like 20 30% engagement. Okay, at least one in three people are chatting but
Also, there are sometimes five dislikes and I'm six dislikes
Wow, I mean that's he's away from not only the lights, but there's not even that many lights. There's like, you know
I mean, there's sometimes more than others.
Sometimes there's zero dislikes,
but most of the time people are disliking it.
I mean, it's like,
I just think probably the same few people just haters, right?
This time this had eight, wow, eight people dislikes
Freaky Friday last week.
I mean, it's like, yeah, so it's kind of like,
and if it gets more people don't like it than do like it,
that's, wow.
So you get, hey, Spunky, how are you?
I'm here, how are you?
Do you hear me, guys?
Okay, so I'm sorry for thinking you had AIDS.
That's really rude to say, that's really rude.
I mean, even to repeat that kind of stuff is completely rude.
Okay, so then it goes over all the comments
that I get in the chat.
Okay, then it goes over my milestones.
So here's my milestones.
It says I've achieved 250 uploads.
the 125,000 views by July 4th, that was 125,000 views.
2,500 subscribers, July 4th, and 200 uploads, July 4th.
So July 4th was an important day for me, okay?
I mean, that's basically what it tells me right now,
but I think I'll be able to hopefully get more value
out of it.
It has some stuff that you can use
to fix keywords and stuff like that.
How are you guys?
So who's halo get into 500 subscribers for the halo reveal. Hmm. Let me see
I know halo was halo weren't you trying like you're you're you're saying like weird things like you're also saying
Like you're saying something. Hey Nancy. How are you?
Hey money for 20
Yeah, hey spunky he is a dog who's about
Oh, yeah. Oh, hey, okay. Hey those call Justin right now and get into stop tell him stop reading our relationship
The end of Europe about to break up with him
He's like, okay. I got it guys in talks instances. I guess, right? I
Guess if someone can
Uh, so are you sure, but okay, I guess I guess spunky knows I guess God is good at like talking to another man
I think God II but God II give me advice. I probably
go search for the nearest pier and jump off of it, but
Justin is going to get good advice from God. I'm sure God is not got even nice to other people
He's a great therapist. Yeah, I mean, it's like that's like, you know
Like a man's a man's therapist like no, I don't think I'm enough of a man's that she gives advice
Okay, oh shit. Yeah, so I was on
It is like an hour last night, you know, and then I was like you smoke weed. That's your therapy
I don't know if that's like good
like a weed smoking it every day gave me like a really bad anxiety like it was supposed to take away
anxiety but it ended up like giving me anxiety like more anxiety like in the just like the
I had to like really cut down a lot on it to get I was so addicted to it though now I'm not
addicted really to it anymore it's like I can go without it hey trix okay we give you paranoia
So I just been hitting the is this almost gone. Oh my god. Yeah, it's a vape. It's almost gone already. It lasted a little over a week
They will be a couple more
Yeah, but we had a guy lead a fun night on DJ Electra's show
I think it is a lecture fry or this hack for pack ride studios and
It was her birthday yesterday
And it was just fun.
I did some readings, went for her co-host.
You need to find the right strain that works for you.
But it is hard because it's like in California,
everything's so strong.
You know, it's like everything is like the same.
Like, it's like, it's like almost like hair,
like really like an opium.
Hi, Spunky.
Oh, no, no, no, you're fine.
This is, this is a place to like,
Discussed all that kind of stuff plus I can give you you know your cards on hey, I want to show you this really cool
Little deck I got it's right here
Yeah, I don't want I want to do it was for spunky because she got me to put it this is like it may
Not to say this is anybody in your life, but this is haters exposed and it says evil. I
Oracle cards, and so this is like sometimes if there's something toxic going on
And we can see but it's really cool cards to people the cards look like
And it looks like they might have been written in like somewhat kind of like other country
I'll read the back box to you because it's interesting it says
This deck of cards exposes the haters, an excellent deck for investigating the eye of evil, and also an excellent therapy for treating certain mental problems.
I strongly recommend this set of cards.
Their intentions towards you, their feelings and opinions towards you expose.
Hatred can help you understand their hatred towards you and others.
Why do they dislike it? What are the reasons and so on?
The information conveyed by this deck of cars
is direct fax and incredible.
It does provide a detailed analysis of who is toxic,
where it comes from, and possible recommendations
for addressing toxic environments.
Manufacturer C. Shui.
Now, I mean, so it obviously was written in China
or something, but that's pretty cool.
I mean, they were like, hey, we're gonna go with them.
Fuck spell check or grammar check.
Just say what we want to do, using your mind.
Okay, so I'm going to pull you five cards
because these are a lot of them.
There's a lot of them actually.
Look how many of them, these are a lot.
So there's five, I'll pull you five
because they kind of like,
sometimes they give remedies or sometimes they give a diagnosis.
Okay, one, okay, two, okay, three,
ooh, uh-uh, okay, four, okay, five.
Ooh, okay. Well, is there advice or is there some kind of like big message?
Mmm, okay
I mean, I don't think this is about Justin this could be about this could be about anybody anybody
I mean this could be resonating with anybody, but here's where it lays out
Okay, we're dealing with a spirit that is a trickster spirit. So here's a picture of the trickster spirit
It says sudden loss of memory things end up missing
So you sometimes your mind is playing tricks on you. I don't know
So is this there's somebody in your life that maybe is not being honest and has like this like you know mask on
Okay, and then maybe that's their spirit ruling that was a trickster spirit, right?
You don't like seeing, yeah, you have empathy, Jenny.
Yeah, Jenny, Jenny, were you on like,
cause like someone named Juice the show,
like did a something about,
oh, say he did a show about like,
or is this the sort that you think,
oh, say he's, you know, hitting on male guests
or something like that.
Or he's like, he's, another working master of it.
Edgy he's edging to the guests and so okay, so anyway, there's like 15 people
I saw I found the video that they caught he clipped my show like two minutes for I was just joking saying people were edgy
watching my show and then
And then people in a shower. Oh my god. He's so disgusting. He's disgusting and then it's like another somebody named Jenny Jen
That was like, oh, he's a disgusting predator. And so I was just I don't think that was you but you don't go to the channel
Yeah, there was someone named Jenny Jen. I was like, oh my god. That's not Jenny
Hey, there's a trickster spirit maybe operating, okay?
So maybe, take a second, look at what the person is saying.
Then this one says,
possess an amulet and have it blessed with protection.
So there's a remedy for this spirit.
Just yeah, okay. Just okay. That's why I got confused. It was just yeah. She hates me
I was like, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to confuse
Yeah, this is like also likes some protection like you know, she's taking a photo or something like that
But it says that's an amulet and have a blessed with protection
Who who does oh juice, yeah
Okay, so they're so an amulet you might want to get an amulet right the remedy is just in these an exorcism
Yeah, maybe but also it says stealing your ideas pretending they invented them
Okay, so I don't know if this is you know, this is somebody in your life
But maybe there's somebody that's like jealous and it's like it is they oh, you know saying oh, I you know
I don't know it's like this is like maybe an energy that's at work, too
And I'm not saying this is about me specific person
but we also have
This spirit team is, this is your spirit team.
It says ancestors, angels, spirit guides, gods,
goddesses have your back, okay?
So you have protection against all these sick,
all against all, and so I say their spirit team
in conjunction with some kind of like blessing
you do on an amulet and maybe carry for protection.
And maybe we'll help with some of this trickster energy
and rival energy because you also have,
this happened to me recently, unexplained body welts,
bruises and scratches.
I don't know if I woke up one day like with this that burn. It's still there. Look it says it says like see you see it I
Woke up with that. I have no idea where it came from. It was like it was burned in my arm. I woke up. So yeah, I had that unexplained
thing, right
Okay
And when I ask what's the whole thing is basically, yeah, there's like an evil eye out on you a little bit
Maybe that could be affecting
Relation if someone is jealous someone that is like this is business rival
I don't know if they're a fellow medical person or something but someone cannot stand your grind and hustle
They don't like it. And so maybe they're putting this negative energy and sometimes negative energy
There's sort of this because we're so we're empaths
Sometimes it will play out in us and stuff. So I hope that was interesting. Okay
I was talking about you.
Oh yeah, I was talking about you, because you did.
But you flipped my show, where I was joking, saying,
oh, my audience edges to me, and I edge to my audience.
And then all these people were just talking shit
and then in your thing, I was more first in the world.
And I was like, wow, this is what I get
for letting people borrow my clips.
I'm like, yeah, everyone can share my clips,
and then everyone just talks shit about me.
No one defends me.
Okay, so let's see.
So it says who don't make me jump through the phone. Damn it. Well, she's you know
You did you clip my show and I'm not gonna ever go against
You know people to be my show. I know it's a clip it like why was but the chat was like saying I was
Your or your bet on the messages. They're saying we'll shoot about me. They're like saying oh
You know like he's a bad person and
Who why are we so watching this f a g g o t is stuff like that? I don't know
I don't like that
Anybody else want an evil eye card is the haters exposed card anybody else want a couple of these cards
Oh, someone's having these kind of problems or they feel like you know evil life. I suggest a couple of remedies actually
spiritual baths
Anointing with maybe an oil putting your attention in it
Okay, yeah, there's you're like anointing like you know with oil it's very symbolic, but
I've noticed it can kind of like
free the mind a little bit.
Okay.
Yeah, I spoke, I think,
okay, I'm going to expose you with the cards.
Yeah, let's pull some for Ilya.
Oh, I'm not going to expose you, but Ilya,
maybe this is you, maybe it's somebody in your energy,
but let's like, let's look at that.
I'm going to give it a nice shuffle.
Okay.
You don't like seeing anyone hurt it. Yeah, because because an MCAT that hurts it hurts them because they realized we're so connected
That it's like well our suffering is actually we all cherish our own suffering, right?
And it's like we don't want other people to take our suffering because we were like I
We have kind of like have a badge a badge of honor right by putting up with our suffering. Okay. What do I have for Ilya?
Okay, Ilya. Okay, I'm gonna do three cars plus the big big message. Okay, three. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh
Ilya
Okay
So yeah, it has a remedy too. So look at this
It says you got two of these so the person causing your negativity is an air sign and the person causing your negativity is an earth sign
Okay, so maybe there's it's just these two haters or something. Yeah, there's so it says there's an air sign and earth sign
That are
Causing you negativity they're projecting negative energy towards you. Okay, then
We got the first you get these are the remedies are recommended. Okay, so what versus tigers eye, okay?
And it says helps with grounding protection self-confidence inner strength will power
Clarity, okay, so that is a good maybe since they're getting some tigers eye jam, right?
Also, it has polo santo polo santo is a wood. It's very sweet smelling
It says smooth spicy aroma clears out negative energies. It's those calm and relaxation fills your home with joy and harmony
So smoke smoke out the issue basically, okay? I have a tiger's eye and the smoke, okay?
Yes, okay
Anybody else like a card? I think I'm cool with you. I am I was just texting yesterday
We're cool, we're cool
Yeah, it's like where we all go through like, you know, or I go through bitchy days, right? We're on bitchy. So
And women sometimes men are like just like just like always bitchy and then like women sometimes we'll get the
extreme like the monthly and then it's like the rest of the time be pretty good
But men are always kind of annoyed, right? I
Don't know if it's
I don't know if I'm being stereotypical or anything.
Are you like the glasses?
I mean, I'm also getting some new glasses today, so.
Okay, so, okay, Dancy wants some cards, I think.
Okay, Dancy, I'm gonna pull five cards from Nancy, okay.
Okay, one, two, okay, three, okay, four, okay, five.
And I'll do one one more. Okay
Okay, Nancy, we also have an earth sign. This is the person causing your troubles in earth sign
We also got this bodily unexplained bruises and stuff in your sleep. Maybe
loses as well body scratches keep an eye for those like little signs, okay?
Then it says they'll claim I did it first knowing damn well. They got inspired by you
So this is someone that's jealous, you know, that's what our root of the evil eye is jealousy
It's called, you know, the evil eye or you know, it's envy and he is the sin, right? This one says
I think it says P charge your energy,
but I think it means recharge your energy.
It says distance yourself, take a break, vacation,
pamper, indulgence, do the things that make you most happy.
So recharge your energy, okay?
Recharge your energy, maybe, but this one says
they are recruiting haters, okay?
So somebody's like, you know, saying stuff about you.
And they also are claiming credit over your success.
I mean, it's like the advice here
which is basically to recharge your energy.
You're gonna need to maybe go into hermit mode
a little bit, you know, it's like just the,
cause there's, are you feeling some of the negative energy?
Okay.
I hope that makes sense because I'm trying to see
if they have some advice for Nancy.
Okay, also Nancy, it says they're keeping tabs
on your every move.
Hey, Electra, how are you?
I'm pulling some of these,
these are really cool cards, Electra.
I just got these new cards.
So I don't, this is called the Hater's Exposed deck,
but it's kind of like about,
wow, there's a lot of cards in it too.
Like it goes into like, you know, remedies
and also like, like some diagnoses, I'll pull.
Let me see, let me see.
So I got for a lecture,
you will witness their karma, okay?
So this is already justice.
Before we say anything, right?
What else we got for a lecture?
Causing you to miss out.
That's what they're trying to do.
They're causing you to miss out
or lose some kind of opportunity.
So don't be dissuaded.
It's like, oh, I'm not gonna pay attention to this or this
because someone like dissuades you.
They might be trying to like you not interested.
You also got this unexplained body well scratches. There might be some kind of you know, succubus incubus spirit of vault
but also says Mars retrogrades
Impulsive rage or a banger, hotility major blowout spikes violence. I think we are in so this Mars retrograde
I think that maybe when energies kind of get crazy because Mars is you know, the planet of fire
Planet of war and when it goes retrograde
Yeah, definitely causes out was kind of that outbursts and people I've noticed mercury retrograde to they are
Kind of specific heat ship and zip Christine said Jamie's told her to get face reconstruction surgery
But when Jamie's was talking about it, she didn't get it or tell Christine that
Hmm you had to put a spell on those who use your photos and they get away
Is that interesting crystal? Can I pull a card for you or pull the cards for you?
Yeah, but you what if you'd like out of this deck because it might have the interest on the interesting you had a great birthday
Thank you. Yeah guys. I was I did tell people to like go watch that but
That episode is still upright. I can go get it. Yeah once I got
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh, hold on
Wow, hold on shit
With I okay, so first of all would like some cards, okay, is that okay?
That's my room is like I seem like I was like having a lot of fun on your show
I look sure but yeah guys here look at this. It's on hack rise channel, and yeah
This link is here. Yeah, is this the same one? I'm here like yeah, he's the same
Oh, yeah, look at there's like if just does it guys take out that like little it's just like a little clip of something
I think it's really funny though. I think you'll like it for crystal Marie. Okay. What do I got?
Okay, one okay. Wow, okay
Three okay, I'm gonna do one more
Okay, so crystal
This says someone is causing chaos and fights in your love connections
Okay, so there may be some negative energy being thrown at you with like evil eye or voodoo or something towards you causing chaos in your love life
Okay, and then it says a
Return to sender backfired on them and so I think you might have done a return return to sender and it really like
Backfired on them. So they got shit on themselves, right? It's like they
And so I think it was effective.
But I think also we have a couple of remedies for,
thank you, Electra.
We have a couple of remedies for crystal.
We have this black obsidian.
It says, carries a calming and positive energy
that can help you remember to look
on the bright side of things.
Okay, so black obsidian might be like a gem
or a stone you wanna look at.
Oh, I think Jamie,
Jamie's cab was
No, unrelatable. They don't you don't like those words. We're empathic
Yeah, well, we know Jamie was in a terrible car accident and you know, I think she has x-rays or something tomorrow
So she told me like she wants to do you know 20 or go on today
So I was like, okay, I didn't go on hey, but I also do I'm crystal. This is the this says
There's you get an amulet. I was a good get a black obsidian amulet some things to wear
Black obsidian is very good at like just spelling a negative energy, especially because it's like the natural black stone, right?
So all this anything black anything negative will basically go into this obsidian. I
Think those are the remedies it sounds like also, you know how to do return to sender and that that back so it was backfired on that so
Okay
Yeah, where is the mohawk girl much? Who's the mohawk girl?
Okay, so cool. I mean, I'll do one more card cuz that was like four
I'd like to like a number like five cards. Oh, it says there are their social media posts means are directed towards you
So that's there might be somebody that is like posting and they're like, you know being passive aggressive about it
I've had that problem with people like, you know
it just seems like everything is like relating to me
and like sometimes maybe it's not true,
but it's like, you know, sometimes when people are postings
and it's just a little bit personal,
like they're saying, I'm like, just basically,
so I just think we understand, but nobody else does.
Okay, aw, yeah, yeah.
Well, I don't know if I have this,
Jamie didn't show me this picture of like a spirit.
Let me see if I can still have it.
Yeah, I don't know if you guys can see it was if you like close close up on this picture of the car
I mean and it's because it has a
Like some kind of scary like witchy looking thing in the passenger seat. I don't know if I still have it. Let me see
Do I have it still yeah, I do
I'm sorry to downlay too many things, shit.
Well, it says okay.
I think I'll just, she shouldn't be showing.
Hey, Vicky, how are you?
Hey, this is NorCal.
Kiss me now, Jamie has,
well, it's trippin' sip, we don't know,
like she might be going through.
I pull your normal car, sure, sure, sure.
Do you want like a rider weight?
Yeah.
I'll play you three right away
And then maybe we'll do
I'll death the card right away. Okay, so it's like whatever is happening. It's like you're protected
Okay, so this is the four of wands and I think so there may be some kind of like
Passion in the home right now, but it's like, it looks like, you know, ultimately you can work together
You know, it's like in you're protected and safe
And so just like imagine that set safety around you and you know
Sometimes we take things out on people closest to us sometimes
Is that yeah, I think you're both really guarding your happiness. You're the arms cross right there like yeah
No one's gonna get this like you know in better process, but it's like happiness is also like, you know meant to be shared
And so this is like also the rainbow that's similar to the 10 of cups, which is like the ultimate happiness
Right, so it's just like basically
Both of you or maybe you're like, you know, sitting like they're like, oh, I don't but so you can reconcile because oh
We have the tower. Okay, so the tower is like a little shake-up and that might be happening now, too, right?
Let's get a couple more cards for this. It's like, you know what I always my dad would always say is like
Oh never go to bed angry. And so just like sleep on things. Okay, sleep on things not not in a good way
Let meditate asleep
You will think of things differently in the morning.
It's always good to give it a little rest.
If there's like a big thing and just continue to work
on things, maybe you can ask another couple
like what they think about or something like that
or maybe somebody else wants to help you out.
Here's a couple going to somebody and like giving advice
like you know, okay advice for spunky.
I would say like kind of like, you know, he's like this kind of page of walls is kind of like he's just like a hot head
So he's kind of just immature and he can be forgiven because he's like a he's passionate
and sometimes he gets angry and stuff like that and he's a little bit exuberant maybe but
Can be forgiven because of the kind of like the innocence to it. He's not really trying to be
An asshole, but you kind of just works out like that sometimes
Post the streamer link, um, okay, but you see where's a VIP panel say would you would you think that you're belong on the VIP panel?
I'm only have very important people
Just kidding. I'll put I think you're important
You're worthy say okay, so a spunky also do like the audacity card because it's so cute some of these audacity cards are really cute
It's called the audacity deck
The audacity there's like a little okay
We get an audacity car for spunky. These are like less explanatory
Like you know, you might have to do three. I'll do two of these cards. Okay. First. We have the cold shoulder
Okay, so who's doing the cold shoulder is that you or him like someone's doing the cold shoulder
This is also number 15 number 15 is of course the devil card and so
Close cold shoulder. They dropped the link. I did okay
Hold on a second. I'm gonna do one more for spunky. Like I said, okay spunky. We also have the moon. Okay
Yeah, this is this is cycle. This will everything there's a moon right there. Yeah, everything will work out. Okay, it's just like and because number
six
We have number six and number 15. That's the lovers and the devil basically right like six or 15 because that five
Plus one six right spunky. There's something meant meant to be in this. So just the normal relationship stuff
It is mercury out of Gatorade
Hold on one second. I might keep on clipping
Yo, what's up? Hi? How are you?
Nothing
I like your girl friend. I'm chilling in my girlfriend's room. I just fucked her asshole
You don't have a girlfriend and I know I know enough to know that I was finished clapping cheeks
They go well, you know, hey, hey, first of all say a blow up doll does not count as a girlfriend
Okay, first it's got a pulse and it breathes
What is an animal or mineral or vegetable?
It's a human being with a soul
A woman is it a woman or a man? But is it your friend? What's that guy got me this Georgie the glow she gave me some
Is it are you talking about 300 glow that you have his butthole or no? No
No, okay. Cheers. Thank you. Okay. Don't say the n-word stop saying the n-word, okay?
I'm gonna say whatever I would like. I'm not saying anything against to us
Yeah, but don't I don't you don't tell me that I have the right
Everybody go up my show say I think that's my so anyway
I told you not to say it don't argue with me if I say that okay
I mean I have nice enough to have you on you but you know at least they respect my show a little bit
You're not going to whatever
Okay, I don't like playing just two cars that's funky one more card for you
The gardener, okay, it's about taking care of these nursery things, maybe pouring some water on stuff.
There's a little bird there that maybe like, you know, like, give you some good advice, too.
These kinds of cars are kind of scary because they're all, you know, there's a lot of skeletons in them.
But, you know, just to remember that, like, you know, life is, I love you too.
Life and death are intertwined in a wonderful, wonderful, weird way, right?
I think they're, they both are part of life.
Okay.
But I think it's pretty I love you, too. I think it's a cute little deck. Oh Tommy Tommy James is here Tommy James is here to argue
Where's my uh hold on I also have my uh Christina Ricci deck. Where is it?
My right it's called cat full of spiders. I don't know if it is right here. Oh
Where is it? I
Just heard a beep, okay. Oh, oh here it is, okay
So here's the Christina Ricci deck, it's so cool, it's called Cat Full of Spiders.
A lot of it looks like her, it didn't have the guidebook in it, even though it says it doesn't unbox, I think so it must be actually.
And knockoff, but it's still a good deck, I need to download the PDF of the...
Of the how she describes the cards I want to hear her thought process behind some of them, but I'll do a
Collective I'll do probably okay. Hold on. No, I'm gonna just say I'll hold on
I'm here this Christina read you reading first and then we have nor Cal. Hey, traveling ZFC. Thank you for
You know shouting out your member highlight. Thank you so much. We have nor Cal here. Hold on one second
So make sure it's a real Nor Cal. Oh
Hold on where's my Monday
It's just another Monday
Hello, what's up big dog? Hey Norca. How are you? Hey, I like that strong hand you took with siggy fucking took him backstage
I'm slapping him around like a beotch
Yeah, I mean I'm not gonna hear let's let him run run
You know they tell me tell me what's against COS when I'm dealing with you. Yeah
Was rumble COS
What do you say
Rumble yeah, so you can basically like you know
Do anything on rumble. I have to worry about YouTube, which is the biggest, you know
Platform in the world and so it's like it's a little bit different than rumble a little bit
So he's he's an election to be about to us and he's had his show, you know
He's banned from YouTube basically, so I just don't I don't want to hear it. Oh look I can see Jenny girl Jinjin
She's got me blocked for some unknown reason. I don't even really know her
I mean, but that's okay. Go ahead and keep me blocked. It's a big W
Just like Crystal Marie's got me blocked, but I know why she does
Because I showed a fucking goofy picture of her smiling with her dolphin teeth
Flipper flipper faster than lightning
No one you see
I don't think well, I don't think that she's like anything like super at all. But I'm pulling some out of these uh
These cars for the chat. Let me see. Okay. We have okay. Wow. We have a camera
Wow, one second guys. I'm gonna do one more. Okay, so okay, so this this reading right here is about
Cuffs and so there's like a lot of happiness you have like, you know
It's like as baby
You're just happy with your your animals and your cats and stuff like that because this woman's very very happy with her
But she has and she has some cuffs out for her cats and the cats around her, right?
What is this about those it's not something about your happiness, okay?
So we have the Eight of Wands. So there'll be news about something happening really quick,
and it has something to do with a lot of money, because those are the Ten of Pentacles,
which is the, which is the generational wealth and the Christmas and whatever.
Also, we have someone very happy, just outside of material wealth, there is wealth of the world.
And so what is this she has in her hand? She has these little like, you know, coins. And so
That is a her form of abundance and so, but just remember the real wealth is that if the world wealth is not in things, it's in things that are not things.
That's the real, the real, the very important things in life. The most important things in life are not things. That's, that's my lesson if anybody.
There's
I'm doing good bro a real wealth is a cat slithering in and out of your legs
Waiting to be petted or fed or waiting just for any type of or nurturing or a child
We're waiting for their father or their mother to get home and welcome open arms from the daycare
Getting excited maybe maybe getting a slut a slur a slurpee, you know after a long hard day, but um
I just wanted to make a public apology to Crystal Marie.
I apologize for using that photo of you
that you let the internet see.
I apologize.
I'm a big fan, always have been.
I'd like to interact with you again, Crystal Marie.
Please forgive me.
But you just insulted her by saying it's a matter of teeth.
That's not a very good way to do it.
That's what we do in the community.
We come from psychic.
Insulting each other is a form of,
It's like, you know, bullying a girl on the playground because you have a crush on her.
I'm not saying I have a crush on her. I'm just saying that type of hyperbole in the banter.
That's what we do in this community. We give each other shit and we hug it out.
Okay. Well, as long as you know, as long as you like, you know, really want to be friends,
because you were just calling her flipper and now you're like, you know, seeing her phrases.
Well, I'm not singing her praises. I really just was making an apology. I mean look she'll make fun of me too
She knows what I look like she calls me old and weird and I'm a panty collector. She's called me weird things to psych
I'm not you know you collect passes. No, I don't I don't collect panties. Okay, sir
You're married. Yeah, you collect your wife's panties. No, I don't collect her panties
I mean we've been together a long time sir that that dog ain't gonna hunt no more
Okay, you know if I pick up I pick them up to wash them I use my little pink, you know, I'm gentle
He's one of those like
Hold on you've asked multiple women in the community for their panties NorCal is that yeah, yeah, that's what I do
That's what I do ask you but you're married though. All right. You're married. You're asking women for their panties
A sentence in a chat room and you're gonna stand on it. I thought you I thought you agree. I thought you just agree with that
No, I didn't you didn't listen long enough
I'm sorry long enough
You've asked multiple men for penis pictures. I know that's true
matter of fact
I've only received two them from two men, right? Yeah, and so I think I haven't really been successful
And it's not like I've been I'm getting like tons of kicks. I can't I can't barely get a dick
Let a little picture of a dick, right?
Listen, I have an exclusive Tommy James little pink mushroom on a better red cabbage. If you're interested five bucks
I know I'm not interested. I'm not interested. Okay. I'm not interested.
Tommy James, I tried bro. I tried
Okay
Well, North County, do you want a few of these evil eye hater cards or no?
It's you got why are they are they for me personally? Yeah, they're for you. I'll pull some for you
I would enjoy that
Okay, so what I got for NorCal, okay? I want to see you shuffle them like all the other all the professionals do and shuffle them and let
One fly out. Yes, sir. Okay. Well, okay, so here's
Damn devil cards on me now. Okay. Well, we'll see what happened. Thank you, sir
Okay, I'll pull one more for it. Okay
Okay, so I'll put this as a picture.
So here's what it says.
Our worst enemy says you cause most of the problems
or most of the bad things that happen to yourself.
Okay, so we always have to realize
we are basically our own worst enemies.
And so sometimes if we internalize this,
we can curse ourselves just by the negative self-talk.
And so it's like, we have also the most power
over ourselves too, we should.
And so don't be your own worst enemy.
Because our own problems, but then we see it says that you're you have a hater and someone is jealous
It says secretly jealous and hating on your romantic relationship
And so somebody sees you know, you've been married even though you're just like oh you don't have sex anymore with your wife
Or rarely, it's uh, you know, it seems like you know
Stable connection a happy stable connection and some somewhat rather work
It also says hating on your creativity and ideas. I don't know if there's someone that rings the bell with this
But it does have a remedy. It says lavender sage. It says clears away negative thoughts energies harmonize the mind enhances intuition
Inspires loving feelings. And so maybe pick up some lavender sage. It's gonna be that sage wrapped in a little bit of
You know the purple lavender on it. I'm on it. I'm on it. I'm on it
Yeah, I think that will I think that will clear out a lot of stuff. But then you know, we're also thank you
Thank you, by the way
We're we are all our own worst enemies, right?
Right. It's like, it really rang to me. I, I might, I might change my life like I did when I went to Burning Man.
Yeah. Well, it's like, we often do get in our own way and we often are harder on ourselves than anybody else can be.
We worry a lot about other people think about us, right? We put a lot of energy in that.
It's something we can't really control to a great extent what other people will think about us.
They're mostly thinking about themselves most of the time.
We might cross their mind here and there
in a positive or negative ways,
but depending on their mood and all kinds of factors.
And so, we can only really, yeah.
Yvonne, what are you talking about?
Who about what you said your last comment?
What is that about?
That's wild.
Who's talking about that?
and Bonas says, wow, oh my God, how would you be
as someone who hates, how would it be,
how the fuck, why does it have to be
with someone who hates your, well, I don't know,
does somebody hate your, oh, no, no, no, no,
so she's talking to Spunky, she's talking to Spunky
and I think it's like, it's just girl talk,
let me let the women talk it, talk it out,
they're gonna figure it out.
That's crazy, Spunky, I mean,
I was with a woman one time that had a super autistic child, and I love that child more than anything I
Still still I'm still in contact with him
Jim Carrey
Wow
I want to introduce this I do this tarot card it is of actually based on spunky and Justin here we go
How you like that one. That's pretty cool, huh?
Hi, Real and Nancy.
Spongebob, do you like this one?
Let me see what he got there, sir.
Interesting. The threesome.
Well, if you look at the devil card, it is with three people like that.
It's like, you know, got the...
On this there's also the Lubbers card. It's also the same kind of layout on the Lubbers card
And which is like, you know, there's like Raphael and then there's you know bathroomette on the devil card, right?
But they are different
it's kind of like the difference between Hades and Hades and
Zeus, you know, they're basically the same day to you under a different frequency a different
material realm and so I
Have a sort of baphomet as my profile picture
Okay
Well, so that's a
Transformer a little bit
I hope you're okay, spunky. I hope I hope you're okay. Okay. Who needs men when there are dildos?
Well, you know Ariel from the Little Mermaid had a dildo collection, but she called him thing. I'm a bobs and
thing of a bobs and
Whatever I forgot what's a thing. I'm a bobs and I
Got gadgets and gizmos of funny. I got who oh who's this and what sits?
me site
Yes, I've probably been to the Rocky Horror Picture Show a hundred times
Yeah, it was like that it said show at the movie theater where they like
The midnight movies yes, but I've been I've traveled around and went to the play
They just had here around where I live. They have a plane went to that as well. What do you think about that?
I actually love the me I like I love some of the music in that it's like a kind of a weird movie that I don't really understand
A hundred percent. I mean, I do get a lot of it now
But it was not when I was a teenager and I went to the move a midnight thing where they threw tortillas and stuff in the audience and
Acted out in the on the stage alongside the movie
Interesting experience. It was an interesting movie. You have to watch it several times to actually get the get what it's about
It's it's about the transformer right so it was about people that are attracted to them
We you know coming to grips with their inner selves their inner self of being attracted to homosexual activity
Transsexual activity all those types of things. There's people that live their whole life
Gay but never go through with the their inner demons. I don't want to call it inner demons, but they're in
They think it's their inner demons. Yeah, it's really who they really are
Well, I think, I think we're like human beings are so comp, you know, the human brain is the most complicated thing in the universe that we found, right?
It's like there's nothing more complicated than the human brain. And so we're so many things, like we're infinite beings in these little finite, finite, limited bodies, but we're infinite spirit.
And so being both is, it's gonna be frustrating. Yeah. And it's like, but
Like that card you just had that was the devil had a woman at a man so he had to admit their disposal chained up
There's a man that I know that lives in New York. It's also fighting his inner inner homosexuality
But we'll save that for another day and I'll die fast. Okay. Well, is that somebody I might know too or no?
Okay, well, I'm not gonna say any names. We get guys because we all have our we all have our
Okay, how are you?
But yeah, let's let's like nada. Yeah, we won't bring up any names
NorCal ARP the ARP Association of retired people called you owe money. I think you owe the $25
$25 monthly fee
Godie you're all right, man. No, I'm good
I declined their offer. I declined their offer. Okay, so 55 or some shit for that to even
I think it was 65 or 55. I think 65 is the senior citizen 60 and they might be 55 now because
55 is in his 65 but um I don't know um senior citizens are getting younger and younger nowadays
everyone wants to discount at a denny's right nor Cal's a member of your
I wish I was all those things. I wish I was old enough to retire. I'm not though. Yeah
That's what happens when you have a family to take care of you have to work hard to
Make sure they have the things college funds money put away each month thing
So that your kids can go to college that kind of thing you want a better life for your kids than you had right?
Uh, well, right, but that's why I don't have kids, you know
You don't have kids because you're homosexual, but you can I you can adopt. I mean, I can't I get better
But I wouldn't they think I have cats and they're they are plenty of
You know, it's weird about a cat is
They're not like a dog. They can it's like when they really look at you and they're looking in your eyes
They can see inside your soul and they can tell if you're bad. Yeah, I know this one guy that had a cat and
Yeah, the cat would fucking spray over everything and and the cat was fixed
He just kept pissing on all his shit because he fucking hated them
Yeah animals dogs dogs can't shoot like you know animals are like they see things
We don't see they might see a demon like see on our shoulders like that that we don't see or they might see other other
Dark entities that we that are unseen. You know, they would but uh, they are they are very sensitive
Preachers, and I think they are good at maybe protecting us sometimes like chasing in the spirits bad spirits away
And in person like I said without that story to why would anybody on the internet make that shit?
I've got that would some random ass fucking shit. I pulled out of my ass, but the line
Yeah, the last one you don't know everything about me the last four
The last four issues of that magazine all the custom jewelry and that I made every single piece of that
Well, I mean my boss and me did you know, I mean, but I he gave it up to do is easily
Up in the fucking little attic up there
Jerking is gherkin
But you liked you liked you like looking at penises though and imagining them Pierce, right? No, no
I don't I don't I'm not gay. I don't
Magic penis that that was your job. I mean you work for the first body piercer like genital piercer
Right, you know, just like become that. Oh accidentally. Oh, I'm just accidentally my general piercer and jewelry is up
That's like you actually have to have an interest in that
You go ahead and fantasize for me pop
I'm not tan. I'm not fantasizing. I'm just saying that was your job for years. You were you were in the gay and the caster disorder
Was it Castro or no? I worked in
machine
Also, it was all the jewelry to the gauntlet, San Francisco the gauntlet, New York and
Gauntlet, Los Angeles. Those are the only three stores
They were and you were the ambassador that whatever company or your friends you friend group you had they sent you over there to the gays
They're like, oh
Right or no
Listen to me, I'll tell you the story
what they would do there you know what calipers are they're a precise
instrument down to you know one hundred thousandths of an inch
What the people would do at the locations because I was never at a location. I didn't work in any of those stores
Like I said, we owned a machine shop and we manufactured all the jewelry for them
what they would do is they would take a measure with the calipers and
Send me what the measurement was they wouldn't send me the picture of the penis
They would just tell me what his penis size was erect and what it was sauce. So I would yeah
And you won and then you would like a pair of two years or what?
Tell me I mean
That I wouldn't like hold it up to my penis like but you know, you know, it sounds good
But did you you didn't imagine like the hard penis like when they told you how big it was soft and hard
You didn't you didn't like like imagine what it would look like and
Design your jewelry like that or no? Well, I mean I might have imagined what they would be doing with it. How would you?
You're over here you're over zealous you your zeal is too powerful right now, so just listen
What I would imagine was how would they put that with that on there because some of the motherfuckers listen to me
Yeah, you know, you need you know, I use a tape measure, right? You know, there's
1616 and one inch and I'm I need a yard. I need a yard stick
You know, there's 16 16th and one inch one one every
Slash is a 16th with that being said then it goes to quarters and 16th of any way there were some that were several inches
Wow, you get what I'm you get what I'm cooking papa
Was your favorite ones since the time for well
Yeah, cuz they were easier to make the bigger the bigger it is the easier to make now
Let's get back to Tommy James. You know who the six six screw is
Okay, tell me six six six
Is that how big yours is your six inches or bigger?
My it's neither here nor there. I'm I'm I'm blessed down yonder. Let's just say that
Let's not let's not get out of hand now
I mean, what's the biggest one you've ever taken inside of your rectum sir. May I ask that question without being?
I'm not really I'm not really a bottom, but it's probably a black guy, but I don't know how big was it?
Why I didn't ask what color it was
Um, I
Has been I don't know. I don't think it's the whole thing with it. I don't I don't remember I blocked it out of my memory
But you know what I think I took a pinky once I think that's
No, it doesn't I mean it's like, you know, that's why I'm not like a boss
I don't think it feels good there as like, you know
I think you have to like really like work out that that area for a while before like
I don't know I'm like more like I'm actually more of like a
Hugger than like an anal person. I'm not really like those up in the anal stack. That's not like me. Okay. I'm like
What is a hugger? What does that mean? I like to cuddle, you know, my and I want to make out
And I like to like just more innocent stuff than just like penetration with my
Okay, interesting very interesting. So you're a cuddler, I got you
Yeah, definitely. I'm a romantic. I'm definitely a hopeless romantic emphasis on the hopeless and
First and you're funny dude
Yeah, I'll take one well that that's terrible what up, you know, let's you know, I hope everything goes well for you spiky
That's terrible. I mean if what I was reading in chat was true. That's nasty work
Yeah, I've never been I've never been gay. I've never was attracted to men sexually and I've been the burning man at all
Kinds of places. I mean I can appreciate a man if he's handsome and shit, but I've never
It's never you know, you know, you get if you're attracted. I've never had that not even close not once
How many guys have you how many guys we had sex with?
Not one that have not even a kiss
No, no no sexual activities with a man ever
No, never
Not like it not like it not like a like in a locker room like a little towel snap or you know touching tips or
What's up summer are you asking me if I was
If I ever look down in the locker room when I was changing with the other men fuck yeah, I look down everyone does all the men look
The ones that don't look are the ones that are suspect meaning that when you look at it, you go. Oh, I like that or do you go?
I like it. No, I didn't like I told you before I'm not sexually attracted to men whatsoever penis is any of it
Men's bodies, none of that, none of that turns me on whatsoever, but you've had how do women do it though?
It's like men are just like so disgusting and weird like what what are women see in them?
Well, it's there, you know, if they have a nice voice
fingernails
fingernails soft skin, you know feminine femininity
That's a man like a women this women like a women but what a women see a man and say of course men like love women
But but also men see men love women and women are feminine, but then men don't like feminine things
I don't understand is it kind of like a well there's some like feminine things. Um, you know, um 30 diamonds
That that guy loves feminine things a lot. So much. I mean three diamonds the transgender. So, okay
They identify as a female, so
Well, it's like what is gender is gender something fluid or is it like a hundred percent like I think sex is like a hundred percent like you know
It's male or female, but it's like gender is more of a social construct or concepts
Maybe we can fall into either one, but we're born of a being of both genders every man
And then you got the old classic hermaphrodite trick. You got somebody has brought
Now what do you do
Well, that's why you know a lot of parents will decide which one to keep as and so and then they'll make the wrong choice
And then the person's all fucked up and they don't have the you know
I mean it'd be a very big malformity in the first place, but the happen but
You know to be born with both the genitals, but I'm sort of diamond was apparently born with a prostate and so it which is just interesting
Yeah, have you seen many massive on the show? Oh, I've seen many Manson before you were even on the internet
Okay. Yeah
Manson birds from a community called pot awful
That's where he first started going on panels going on streams singing songs dancing for people
His name is Jesse PS. He's a famous youtuber, you know, he's got a famous show. It's called pot awful check it out sometimes pretty funny
It's Pod Hawkins, a host on that show.
It seems like we would go together.
She's not involved in that show.
No.
Okay, I'm just looking at I just found all these books. I had like I'm saved on my drop boxes
I'm just seeing if I found something weird. We see it. This is called
Let's see flowers of Cairo's. What is this? It's a very short thing. I'm just like a real quick flowers of Cairo's
Fucking god
Believe it or not. I come from a high stock and good gene pool believe it or not
What are you up to Goddy? How you been man?
Goddy, how are you? So I was like a I was thinking this would be something
Interesting. It's like that 144. Does the number 144 mean anything to you was 144 mean anything to you at all?
No, not really
Okay, the number 29 and 31 means something to me. Well 29 is like 2 plus 9 is 11
And then we have 31 is 3 plus 1 is 4
11 is 2
So they're kind of big a second square of each other
It's kind of goes along with this because 2 of 1 4 4 like 4 4 is like it's like that
This is the tesseract and tesseract
You know what a tester act is let me look at what it looks like
Is a diabolical creature. Let me see it. Let me see it. I'll embrace it if it's if it's cool
I think I think it's like some kind of shape. Hold on. Let me see if I can find it. It's Hester act
t-e-s-s e-r-a-c-t
Let me see that I need to get bring us up right away. I think it's like I almost remind me of it's a hexagram
Let me see it. There's a hexagram. I don't know if it is it sounds like something to do with Saturn
Okay, tests are acts tests are acts, but does anyone know what it is?
Okay, it is he ESS. We are you see teeth it is a
Okay, here's what it is. It's actually a cube with like a little
Cube inside of it, so it's
Listen looks a little bit dangerous. Okay. I like it. So you're you saying that's what that's my symbol a complex
geometrical pattern
It's a cube inside of a square, okay
And it also looks like this how long which is reminds me reminds me. Oh, look at that. Look at that. It's moving
Look at it does
I like that. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you for blessing me with a complex geometrical pattern with my inner being
Very welcome. What's the most money you've ever wanted a psycho psyche?
I'm not really the good at gambling and casinos, but I have won a lot of money on scratchers
I've won like some scratchers. What's the most money you've ever won on a scratcher?
Oh over a hundred dollars
Several times several times
But you have to buy the more expensive scratcher like the $20 scratcher then you have a one and three chance of winning at least
I played the tickets from time to time. I played the tickets from time to time
One time I was at a casino. It was called Thunder Valley casino in Northern, California. I
Went in with the bag of change. They have a change machine because I didn't have any money. I was poor shit
I'm addicted to drugs so I took and put that in this machine and got a few bucks out didn't win nothing
Went over to my friend and he was just watching him play black tag goes here go over there and play one of those machines
I bet you'll win so I went over there and put 20 bucks in it
I won like 400 bucks and went gave him his money back
I gave him 80 then I went to these other machines sat down and won like 500 and something I hit him
Quick hit, right? It was a type of slot machine. So I'm like, fuck, man, I'm fucking getting it now. Now I'm fucking starting to, you know, feel lucky.
I'm starting to feel like somebody that can, you know, maybe predict or read cards and tell somebody their future.
So then I go into this agent lady goes, oh, you've been been very lucky. I've been watching you. I'm like, oh, okay, cool. Hello.
You know, my name's Matt. You come over here. There's more over here. So I went over to go, you play right here. I bet you win.
So I sat down and she's all you very lucky tonight. I can see you. I'm okay
So I put in a hundred bucks and he did have pushed it a few times
You know pushed it a few more times and I hit a jackpot for five grand
She could see I told you I told you so then I tried to give her some money right because I had the money from the
Other jackpot i hit right i told you give me so much because no no i don't want that i don't want that
Played this one right here i bet you went on it right so i put a hundred bucks in that one
I'm playing and i hit five grand on that one now i'm sitting there waiting to get paid 10 grand
Now leso i know you're very lucky you're a lucky man tonight
Well sometimes you know sometimes we will have those lucky nights, but you know as the rule that the house always wins with the
With casinos right and the fools of fools
Mickey maze would think different all the people that can actually count cars professionally would say different as well
Right, but that's cheating though. I mean, it's not cheating. It's not cheating just because you have
Cheating well, it's not allowed and you can you can see those in Vegas anymore?
Hmm. That's true. That's true
They can they can they consider they consider it a uh an unfair advantage or something like that, right?
Well, of course, it's an object. Well, I think what they do is an unfair advantage
Right, but it's like, but they, but they, but it's their game and so they can make the rules.
I mean, that's what happens when you like, that's right. That's right. That's why you got to,
that's why you got to pay attention and be careful. What's up, Sam, man?
But in somebody's benefit of all there's also those that will change the rules
I mean it's like all the time just be you know, it's like and and then basically make them favor themselves all the time
So was it whoever makes the rules can like actually, you know
Can't be here basically change them and make them, you know
And then then sometimes other people don't know the rules to and how can you play a game where you don't you're not told the rules
That seems like also an unfair advantage, right?
Anyway
The story is do you believe in luck?
you believe we're getting lucky
lucky it's like it's just it's it's probability it's statistic and so they
yeah there's gonna be a there's gonna be a percentage at the time where you're
gonna win it because you know like you know it probably maybe 20% to 30%
maybe some kind of profit which is like you know not
even half the time but that's good enough for some people right
what is it odds of blackjack it's like you know
There's the best odds and because you know and that's not very good odds
Well, here's the thing though if you can count cards, which there's it's not that hard if you you know
Those people if you play single deck clutch and blackjack your odds are great
If you can count cards that way your odds are better and you don't have to like be a
amazing mathematician, you know, I mean, just have to have a decent IQ of, you know, I'd say
it's more like, it's like, it's like stage magic. It's like, if you're like, looking at little
detail, like if you're, if you can do stage magic, I think you'd be probably good at counting cards
or that kind of thing. It's like, it's like having an understanding of
certain
That's much more physics than um, you know magic is physics. That's what stage the stage magic
Yeah, stage magic those I'm saying stage magic is basically just you know, it's like sleight of hands or like, you know
Counting cards we go right right along right along with that philosophy, right?
No, no, no, no being able to count things and being able to you know
Pull the old switcheroo or the old pick pocket is a whole another thing
You know, I mean such stage magician would be a great pick pocket
Well, all stage magicians are, like, they distract, you know, they do sleight of hand.
They will have you look somewhere, they'll have you look at the wrong place.
It's mostly good magician. I ain't gonna lie. I like it. Well, you know, it's not it's not real though, right?
You don't think they're defying the laws of gravity with their
No, we know it. We know that we know there we know stage magic is just a bunch of bullshit
I mean they could say it's like, you know, it's an art, but it's not anything
But what would be the purpose of these magical spells if you're just doing like, you know making a rabbit come out of the hat
I mean, it's like that'd be a very super thing to do. We'd have we already have a rabbit population problem
Like why would I bring more into the world magically?
That's the case is a whole other wormhole rabbit holes you both anyway. Anyway, let's see
I used to live in Southern, California
And I've been to Venice Beach probably a hundred times because I was obsessed with it a little bit
But anyway, if that being said you ever seen them little, you know, the three-card Monty in the
Hide the hide a little peanut or hide the thing in the walnut shell that
They're rigs. They're rigs. Those are like it's completely fake rig breakable games like those are
Those are sucker games like people that play them like they'll have somebody come up and like win
That'll be the dollars pick up a plant and then people think oh you can win and then they'll lose everything
Because you can't it's like they're achieved on the game. It's a shell
Well, if you get some fool up there willing enough to you know, put up his money and gamble against him
Don't hate the player hate the game, right?
Well, yeah, but it's like you that's why you really need to to educate yourself on cons
There's something called the con and when they you know the city slicker comes in to easy money
Which is like very foolish to think that money will come so easily, right?
There's always there's always stuff attached to money
The old snake oil salesman, I got you no snake. Oh, and that's another former deception. I'm flim flam
misdirection
It's like just
The placebo effect
see do you think that's different than what we're talking about but the placebo effect
is almost as like powerful as some actual medications and so maybe it was like we should
consider it kind of like uh as something very powerful like as maybe as dangerous as medication
right if you know people say state and it's like that it's not natural it's like but they think
You're right. There's a costume one more question. What do you think about a bury the turtle in Sandman NYC taking over the gay sector?
You know, it's a day. They just been watching so like, you know, it's like they're both power bottoms. They can't
Finally there's people gayer than me in the community though. Finally. I hate to be the only one
It's like those are like they're like it's right. They're like the drag queens. They're like the roof halls of the panel first
Move over flurry diamonds like Barry the turtle and Sam and are going to be like
Of course you won't food. Thanks for everything Julie Newmark
You made me laugh like that was funny. You actually made me laugh out loud. What do you think about this?
pink fair dough pink fair dough, whatever I mean
Well burdo, you know, I mean the only thing that is really
Um strikes me as anything anything the feminine part about him is maybe
His mouth, but uh, otherwise, you know, he's just another
drag queen to me, but you know good luck to bird or whatever he wants to do
I don't know where we went to identify as whatever. I'm fine with anybody being anything
Yeah, yeah uniform be a
You know a magical creature a monster or whatever you want to be but you know when it comes down to it
Don't forget we're human beings right and human beings are just fanciful
Complicated features, right? Mm-hmm. Very complicated. I heard you mention
You did DMP a couple times. I'd just heard you mention it. I didn't like hear you what you thought about it or
Didn't you say you broke through once or something that you actually got to get into the other
Well, yeah, but if you do GMC like, you know, you didn't like
Several times just so you know
Well, have you like meditated on it or do you like wash stuff on it?
Like you go inside or outside on it because it's a short I've done it both
I've done it in a completely quiet place. I've done it at a party. I've done it different places
So, you know with that being said the said and setting like, you know, where you're doing it at has everything to do with what happens in my opinion
Right, yeah
By myself in a completely silent place, you know, and I was in control of everything by myself was the best experience
I've had doing it
Right
Yeah, I made my bed make sure my you know what I mean to make sure there's nothing weird around me
Even though I just closed my eyes immediately. That is a weird drug, isn't it? I mean, it's crazy that uh
99% of the people that do it have the same experience find that very
You know what I you know what I find myself when I do DMC I find myself
Say yes, I see that I see this but I think what is it? What does it mean?
I keep like looking for like what is it like what it like?
I look like I keep running zero in on like what like what what it means and it's like
It's hard to I don't know. I think I need I say I said to break past that uh that part of it
Get back the illusion give us the illusion because like no second dollars will put a bunch of illusions in front of you
And then you realize the illusions are kind of like the same as real life
But the look the illusions that we see at certain times I know it's interesting
But I did the DMT in a pen is like it was a DMT vape pen and it was so strong last time I did it
It was really really good, but
Basically, I just like felt like I was like jumping out of my skin for a little bit, right?
You're mistaken like once I got got into the place that everybody talks about right you go through the chrysanthemum or the
fractal design once you go into there
It's weird that the the beings in there. I don't know how to explain it, but they're they like the gestures
Well, they didn't look like that to me. That ain't how I saw it. I didn't see him
No, I saw machine elves. It's the mid machine. Well, she knows I
Know about Terrence McKinnon. I know about what he saw. They were similar that but they weren't what he talked about
We saw I think everybody
Thing is different, but they're all the same. You know what I'm trying to say what they think is different
But what they're what's happening is the same
There's there being they're like what I've just seen is their big spiritual beings that are connected to us and it's like our like
Way bigger than us maybe okay. Well, they change size to me
They were small and they got bigger than they were transforming into things like
You know different different
objects for me. It didn't last long. That's the thing. I wish it could have lasted longer. It seemed like, it seemed like it was a split second.
You need to do an MAOI inhibitor. Along with it, it will last a lot longer. That's what they do with it.
It was a while ago and it was a short time in my life, but what I have seen the most interesting and most peculiar things is on Salvia.
Now you talked about gestures, right? You talk about like actual gestures and carnival and that's what had happened there
It was created with a carnival that was
No, I had not said so yeah, I think you should try maybe you should try sure you should because it's very very interesting
I mean you talk about the peculiarity of it dude. It's fucking hard to describe
Many people but that's not that's not it can be it can be evil too. It can be me. It's very mean. You know, I mean it could be
Yeah
It's trying to test you is what it's like testing your fortitude and seeing what you can take and what you can't take
You know what I mean? Yeah, it talks to you scared. You didn't I I'm gonna scare you more
You want to be scared the most thing I tell you
You want to be the most scared you've ever been in your life. Do you think you can handle it? I'm like, well, no
But let's go. He's all good answer. I mean, it's fucking great
You know, it was you know trying to see how scared I was. Oh my god. I don't want that
I don't want to be super scared. Yeah
and then you learn how to deal with deal with that emotion maybe in a better way once you can like
Examine it examine it and come face to face with it. You know, that's kind of exposure therapy in a way
So so how's it going for you man? Are you having how's your life going right now?
My happy. I'm actually like
I just clean my like my my my pool apartment like I just think it's so much stuff and I feel like so much better
I am I have my best month ever on YouTube. I'm just this things are just going really strangely
Well kind of scared. I don't want to jinx it because you know, it's like, you know
It is just good. He's just going good, but I'm happy. I'm happy. She happy the best month on YouTube. You mean financially
Yep. Okay. Well enjoy
Thank you. Thank you the words of Sam and NYC enjoy
Thank you. I will
I'm gonna be able to buy a computer this month and then I'll be able to like really improve my show
I'm gonna get like either a laptop or maybe just
I mean they're going to get like a really good gaming computer, you know, with a VR or I'm just going to get like a cheaper kind of computer and then a VR, the standalone VR headset.
What are you going to do with the VR stuff? Are you going to play video games or what?
Um, well, there's actually really cool stuff to do on VR. You can there's like meditation things in VR
Where you're in this, you know, beautiful meditative land. It's kind of like, you know, it helps you get in touch with the
You know, even though it's counterintuitive like oh, you're using the using the computer to get closer to like, you know
You're inner self. It's actually like it's good to see things like, you know, allusion sometimes
Sometimes I use filters and stuff like there's
Violet flame filter on the TikTok right now. I use that to meditate on it. It's like it's really useful and like
During the violet flame like on you and stuff. It's crazy. I got you. He says funky. How long have you known Goddy for?
Well, you know, what community did you originally come from?
Cuz I haven't really seen you around. I mean, I see you recently but like
You know, they're from the Amish. They're Amish Mormon Jesuits. I think I'm right my right. Goddy
I think I got that right Amish Mormon Jesuits. I don't know
All right. Yeah, they're really there. Oh, yeah, and they're on discord or just they're called the discord brigade, right the brigade
I'm not sure
Okay, that's what I heard
Am I right hold on
Yeah, I'm at the men and Ice the men and Ice okay
Men and Ices those are the Canadian ones, right? Well, no the men and Ices are everywhere. They're not just in Canada
They're just a branch of the
Dunkers, you know what I mean like those type of people
What nights like nights like K and I gs or is it and I gs
Nice met the men or nights like the night's Templar or something or what?
No
I mean, it's like, you know, you know the guy I mean there's castles all over France
You know that they have churches and things like that. They also have like, you know, what's the guy's name? His name was
He's like hold on. He's the guy that was
Uh, the leader, he was, I think he's, the Stroud of Turin is actually him. Hold on. The Stroud of Turin.
Well, let's talk about something that's more our age. Do you know who Noam Chomsky is?
Yeah. He's like a philosopher, political philosopher. Right.
He's a linguist. He's a linguist. Okay. I've seen him on Politically Incorrect, I think.
Bill Maher. Oh, yeah. So you've never read any of his books?
No, he's a little bit dry for me. A little bit too dry.
Well, I mean...
So you think languages dry, you think communication?
No, I love etymology.
It's just like, you know, that particular person
that kind of puts me to sleep.
But I love studying that etymology.
If you read one of his books, you would have no idea,
you know what I mean, just about what he's reading.
Well, maybe he's just, maybe he's just smart for me.
Maybe he's just smart.
A very monotone when he speaks is definitely not
exhilarating whatsoever.
But if you really listen to him, it's all right.
I'm just I I just somebody that I studied a little bit was very interested in because uh
You know language is the way we communicate this way we communicate with everything
Well, and that's it. I mean it's like before the written language, right? What do you know what the all languages come from?
Now imagine not being able to speak words whatsoever and just being able to communicate with uh
You know body language that's how well that's how it was. I mean for a long time
The first people about all that he talks about everything like that. He's pretty good. It's pretty talented
Language language is created as like a mystery school thing basically for commerce
And so it was like spread by the Phoenicians were like to see people also the pirates
You know in a certain way and they would know that they'd have an advantage in being the merchants because they knew the language
And they'd be able to communicate without the people understanding but eventually people got cut onto that that there's
So going on that they needed to learn how to translate so now everybody speaks English at least or
Like some of those crazy people in downtown Hollywood. You see talking to something
You're like, are they really talking to something or are they just crazy?
Well, they might they might see me on the veil that we don't see
Because there is definitely more more than one dimension has been proven solid typically
So maybe they're speaking with their dimensional beings very but if you get stuck in the in the
And that dimension it could be really hard you have to keep one foot inside this dimension to operate in it or else
You know people that's why they end up on the street because it's like it's hard to function
In a good way if you're like seeing too much of the spiritual side doesn't need to be balanced
I think in the in the words of Don Henley in the words of Don Henley
I always love to watch the basket people walk around in mumbling
Oh
What he's talking about is, you know, don't judge a book by its cover type thing those type of things
Don't don't look down on them because there's no telling what you can read into what you want, but uh
No, I agree. I agree
But like people that can live actually on the street and like, you know, and like the people that that thrive on it
I like it and they can be very, you know, there's people in india like aesthetics, you know
and basically do that, and then get closer to God.
Very interesting stuff, very interesting stuff
we're talking about.
Let me ask you one more question before I go,
because I'm going to go take my kid to get some ice cream.
But what do you think about the voices inside your head?
Do you speak with them back?
Do you listen to what they're saying?
Do you think that they're trying to guide you
in a certain way?
Well, I just think like are they my thoughts or are they the thoughts that are programmed into me?
Or are they an actual other being right? And I think maybe a combination of all those it can be
I think that we are a brains are kind of like physical receivers and sometimes they they're receiving thoughts that are not ours
And we we want to take ownership of all our thoughts even though they could maybe originate in our head
We don't have to take ownership of it. We can just like watch some come in and out and just like you know leave come in and leave
And not take ownership of everything we think I got you
Yeah, I think the ones like before you go to bed and the ones that you have when you first wake up are the most
peculiar ones, you know, and I mean those are the most peculiar ones. I think that they're
I depends everybody's different, you know, some people call that God, you know, I mean some people call it God talk and see
You know, well, I mean, it could be God. It could be the devil. They could be the same thing
They could be different things. I mean, it's like or it could just be us and we're just like, you know all these different
All these different things we just have a bunch of different masks
We think of everything as outside of ourself and everything's actually within us. Yeah, girl. What's up?
I mean it was good talking with you psycho. You too fascinating great great talk. I'll see you soon
Congratulations on the success. Thank you. Thank you so much. I appreciate you. Have a great day
Yeah, he's a great kid. He's a great guy. I like I like him so guys you want to hear about like I've always been looking at some of these books
I'm trying to see I saw fowls here guys ever see fowls. Fowls is a great
The book is by John Johann Wolfgang von Goeth.
It says Goeth, Johann Wolfgang von, 1749 to 1832.
He was a German poet, writer, and playwright,
who was dominant influence in German literature.
His primary focus was on the natural evolution of things
rather than abstract theories.
Faust, 1808, a play about the legend of Faust,
who promises his soul to the destructive spirit,
In order to fulfill the desire of encountering light through experiences rather than through his study of philosophy
Okay, so I'll just I'll read the dedication and I'll just read I'll read this throughout the weeks
I'll read more, but I'm just gonna read a short paragraph
It is very it's a little bit
You have to just like listen closely, okay?
Okay, it says ye wavering forms draw near me
again as ever
When ye long since moved past my clouded eyes, to hold you fast, shall I this time endeavor.
Still does my heart that strange illusion prize, ye crowd on me.
Tis well, ye might sever while ye from mist and murk around me rise.
As in my youth, my heart again is bounding, thrilled by the magic breath your train surrounding.
glad days and happy faces. Ah, many dear, dear shades arise with you, like some old tale that
time but half-crazed erases, first love draws near to me and friendship too. The pain returns,
the sad laments retraces life's labyrinthine airing course anew, and names the good souls who, by
From my world have fleeted they do not hear the melodies. I'm singing the souls to whom my earliest lays
I sang disperse
That throng who once to me were clinging the echoes died away that one time ring
Now midst an unknown crowd my grief is ringing. They're very praised but gives my heart a pain
While those who once my song enjoyed and flattered, if still they live, roamed through the wide
world scattered, and I am seized with long, unwanted yearning toward yonder realm of spirits,
grave and still, my plaintive songs and certain tones are turning to harps, ecolian murmuring
Ah! Binds me fast. Tear upon tear falls burning. My stern heart feels a gentle tender thrill.
What I possess as if far off I'm seeing and what has vanished now comes into being
Okay, that's an interesting little dedication and prologue and I hope you like that
I'll continue reading from Faust and we'll go through the whole story
But you really should take out the movie with Richard Burton and playing Faust and Elizabeth Taylor as his
As his like lover that he keeps like wanting to you know conjure up and fall in love with and
He makes basically a deal with the devil to you know have like I guess like 30 years of
Magical fun exciting life and then go to hell, right?
And you can be collected by them up to soft for these
The the the deal with the devil, right? Okay, so anyway guys
Do you like that?
Yeah
Hey, okay, hey Vicky
Okay
Guys I by the way, I have some
So openings for private readings. I know like some people would like a longer reading from me. You can have a how about
I'll do 30 of both of my members. I'll do 45 minutes for
Everybody it's a $25 for 30 minutes either video or on phone
I'll go over all your questions you have of told some several decks. We'll have a whole conversation
I'll do anything else. I talked about anything else you want to talk about. I think it's a good deal
But I have like limited spots for that. So if you would like to I have the cash up right here
There you go. And there's also, I mean, let's just take off my Paypal one.
I'm just gonna edit that up. You guys, if you need the different payment method,
you can just contact me and just let me know. I don't want to put everything out there.
Let's check that. So...
Private 30... Okay, it's gonna be private half-hour reading. Let's see.
Half hour. It'll be either be on the phone or if you'd like to do it on video
I can do this for video or FaceTime. Okay, half hour video reading. Okay, all okay
And I'll just put this banner up
Also, you guys if you'd like to sponsor the panel today, I will accept a
sponsored panel anyone would like that. Okay
save
And thank you very much
Okay
There you can look at the banner right there for the ashef if you'd like to book a private reading and I'll do it in 24 hours, okay?
Whatever is gonna be
Within the next 24 hours best time for you and stuff like that. We'll talk about those yellow banner. Okay, is it a new reading? That's gonna be
Three times the cost and I will do it in speedo and maybe hold on the speedo a little bit at the end
Okay, you cannot tape it though
Little bit stag I know everyone's me to do it a new reading
But I have to do that on chatter bait guys last time that was on tick tock. I got two of my lives. I got
Restricted okay, so the first one because I said
I said, okay, I said follow me.
And then I said, I was saying,
oh, I'm gonna do a follow for follow,
which I never said, but they thought I was saying that.
It's okay, unrelatable.
If you also, you know, if you can't afford that,
just like let me know and.
I'll do I'll do like you know three three shorter readings to I'm just saying it's been it was almost like a long reading
Cuz I know I get a little few complaints about you know
Oh, I want you to do like a long reading. I've done an hour long readings without a problem
Yeah, guys there's plenty of information that will come out of it
Yeah, I think I think it's a good deal
For a woman, I would do it in a speedo.
I would only get naked for a guy, I think, I'm only that crazy, right?
So anyway, guys, I have new glasses coming, I can't wait to get my new glasses, I'm getting
some, I don't know if they're almost here, I'm getting some, they should arrive today.
What time is it?
Oh, it's 4.40, they should maybe already be here, let me check.
The woman I made, hold on, I'll show you this woman I made too, this is wallpaper, wallpaper, wallpaper, where is the wallpaper creator, is the AI wallpaper creator, is it right here, gallery?
Yeah, it should be in here, okay, so this is it, this is it, oh my god, okay, so how do you like this one, pretty cool, huh?
I think she's blonde too. She's blonde, but she has like the dark features in the black wings. I like that. Also, oh
Have you seen Ziggy? I made Ziggy into a demon. I think this might be a bonus card of my deck. There's Ziggy
It says the demon Zigos. I
Don't know. It's something I discussed with my AI. I turned him into a demon. Actually, I think that's an essential
Here's, I like this one here, it was a nice little logo I made.
That one was kind of funny too.
I have more of a goat legs there.
How about that, me as the hermit?
Have actually then they have an old one. That's really old. Oh, I don't have that. They're a good
Anything else
Hi apps regarding Ziggy, how is the demon? Yeah, I'm told things by I'm told things by
certain certain entities
That's pretty cool.
Speaking of Knights, I also got, cool.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you like the AI still too?
It drew me as an angel.
It's kind of like one of the funnier ones it did.
I'll show you a whole lot.
Yeah, nice. I am an angel, but then it made me as a devil too. So it's just very confusing
Where am I as a devil? Oh, I don't have it here, but I have like one kind of like the devil because this one I
Had a whole conversation with Sean J or Tommy James last night, you know, he's like, ah
So annoying
Yeah, so I mean like I think that someone is pretty cool. Thank you miss Liz. Thank you. You're the devil's bunkie. Well
Hold on. I mean look at the picture again
Hold on yeah, I kind of it. Okay, look at it. Look at the look on her face
She looks like a little bit guilty. Oh, yeah, I know what's going on here. Oh
Go
I like how Justin is like this like you know in a speedo like I put him in the speedo
The look he looks he looks scared kind of and I look kind of like ah ha ha I look kind of like
Cool, I don't know
Fantastic, okay, I think I think you guys are gonna like the the tarot deck I make
It's gonna have like a lot of already. I'm like also I have I have the book outline guys
I have the the trollopedia. Oh, I should be a bit part of the name. Okay, but I have a
I have the book outlines. I just need to I'm gonna work to like now fill in the outline and make the book
I'm gonna do a Kickstarter campaign to I
Think I'm gonna do the deck first though. I'm gonna do the deck that come out with a book
I'll do both, because I'm gonna do the deck first,
have a certain amount published.
Am I gonna get my deck printed,
or is it gonna be digital only?
I'm gonna have it printed.
I'm gonna have, I bet it will be expensive, right,
to print these decks.
So I'll probably get into like 20 or something.
I'm gonna do Kickstarter for it.
I'm gonna have, like, whatever the Kickstarter will do,
it'll produce, it'll make a certain amount of decks,
which I'll give to the original donators.
With that money, I'll do a more, more like a,
That's a great plan. Yeah, I really I'm really really able to like make these things manifest right now
Because I have all it also becoming really clear in my mind how it's gonna work
So yeah, I do want to do a really nice printed deck and you know, it's gonna be a very YouTube
panel verse theme, but also like it's gonna be a fun deck for it's gonna be everyone can use it
but people on this show really recognize some of the
Who the cards are based on and stuff?
You know, I have to like, you know, I think I have summer. So let me see. Here we go. I don't hope that that demon went in but
they have any
I mean
Andy, let me see
Um
I was going to try some of these drawings I did like
My drawings are pretty interesting. Okay, I don't know but I don't remember who they are. Who are these people like I drew these people
I don't know who they are really though. Let's see
Like this look
All right back
Stuck, okay
Okay, who are these people? I think that's low key fucking low key hoa
Who is that? It says
Gem gem news gen of gem. Who's that? It says
C L C L L D. Who is this?
There is
Nameless
Nameless, I think our name is nameless. Is there anything nameless? There's person
Who's this one?
It says B B B. I know that is BB
Who's that one? That looks like an interesting person to you
There's Canada dry. Okay. I don't know
So yeah, that's kind of my art style
It reminds me kind of a little bit of like John Lennon's where he just did like quick like lying drawings
But they have a little bit of personality to them. I think
Make fun of a black. No, I would never
Thank you guys though for your
It's really giving me a lot of motivation, support, and love behind these projects.
I think I'll do some Kickstarter campaigns to get funded a little bit, but I need to
figure out how to run one perfectly.
AI doesn't do just do all the work.
I mean, it does a lot of the work,
but it needs to be told exactly what to do.
And so whatever it does,
it's like I'm telling it what to do.
And so it's different than me creating everything,
but say I'm working with the AI.
It's kind of like me outsourcing to like some genius
who gets my idea and can put it into like working condition.
Okay, so anyway, hopefully I'm not being too confusing
or anything.
Okay.
So I got this copy, or did I not?
Cool.
Yeah, so then on TikTok last night,
I got, my first of my live got restricted
because I said, oh, you know, follow me.
I'll follow you back.
So they said, okay, can't do that.
Then I got taken off because it said,
I was saying something else, but I wasn't saying.
It was saying I was like talking about
I was directing people off the platform because I said, oh, you can, you know contact me
You know, it'll do a private reading whatever then they didn't like that. Okay. Well, it's easier home
sort of thing. Hello
Hello, it's it's what's up pretty difficult. No, I don't see are you talking to you run your rumble?
How do you navigate these sorts of things?
Who are you talking about and why are you talking about my soul? Are you talking to somebody else? Hello talking to you gentlemen?
me
Talking to you sir
What's the question your problem?
Do I need to refer to you a serve for you to think that I'm talking to you sound like you're talking to several people?
And I don't understand the question what was the question do I need to refer to you as a serve for you to think I'm talking to you
Damn unfortunate. I know I've got a lot of things to say the question is do you want to hear them?
Probably not because it's like, you know, I don't like unsolicited
unsolicited
Criticism, you know, it's like if I said say tell me how to fix myself or tell me what?
I would listen, but it's like you kind of like bring it because I have I have the humility to say maybe someone else knows better than me
And I won't hear their opinion. I have that
Project you're projecting that you're projecting that from you on to me where it's like you don't care what other people think
So I don't really tragic my friend
for you tragic tragic is that you cannot
Shut up. You just can't
You can't like he has to like be criticism. Oh, it's tragic for me. How about like I don't have to hear about it
How about I just like kick you off and then I don't have to hear anything about it
But having you on makes it tragic because then you think you just like grown on and on I tell you on time after time
You never have a point just whine at me. Stop whining. So
Nobody even cares enough to kick you off the show. I mean, no, you've never been gong, but everyone no one
Did it's like they'd refuse
Ugh, guys, can someone gong him please?
Okay, but I think I was gonna do,
I'm gonna put a third eye on this one, hold on.
Can I do that?
No, I can't.
Anyway.
Hmm, how are we doing, guys?
Yes, I would love to create a release of the deck.
So, what do we have?
Some betting bulls.
Oh, this is cool.
Let's see if I can hear this.
Allow the kids
It's a hard chopper solar plexus
It's so that's just a lot that's sorry, that's that's not if that's the
It goes the leach chakra, the sacral chakra, the solar plexus, then the heart, then the shudo, which is the third chakra, then there's like the third eye, and then there's the crown chakra.
So the sarahasra chakra is only available in the pro version. How much does the pro version cost? Let's see.
I didn't know it was only available in the pro version. That certainly was what I wanted.
I like the sound of it though. These sound good.
It's only 99 cents
Not compatible device, okay
It was pretty though, I like the sounds
Loud
Love it
That's Tibetan bowls. Okay
Thank you from person so I'm gonna look at make playing cards calm
Promotional person okay make
Plank yeah, so I think I'll be able to design them, you know, I
Have a copyright free kind of thing and I don't have to pay
Well, I think I just need to have a friend of that. I want to take out this would size
Let's see, makeplayingcards.com.
Maybe I'll do a playing card back to you.
A Pips, just like a normal one, is the makeplayingcards.com.
Cards.
Here we go. Oh, I see. Add your design. You can do custom cards.
Boxes. Okay. Also the books. This is great. Thank you, person. I might use it. Choose your shapes
and sizes. Test the fonts. Okay, perfect. That looks great. Start your design. I can download
this whole one. Custom deck. Enhancer brand versatility is enjoying a game of cards. I
Okay, yeah, I can design the back of it. Let me see
Focus size big size playing cards tarot size cards as those $2 20 cents
Personalize your own sets of tarot cards with your own design employee personalized your card reading source. Okay
Design my own how much they cost it will be
Oh, okay
Well, it's gonna be a little bit expensive, right? So guys, I think I'm gonna do that probably be
Probably I'm gonna probably start to what's 20. It's gonna be expensive. So I can make 20 decks
They cost $20 a deck and I probably sell it for
$40 or 50
But if I do it for
Hold on. If I make 250 copies, that's 250 times 12.
Okay, that'd be three thousand dollars. Yes, three thousand dollars. I
I mean, I will need to do that many, but I don't need to do 250. I can do 100. I can just do 100 times 14
What's 100 times 14?
$1,400. I can do it. So I'll do half price. Okay, I can do that and then I'll make a hundred decks
There's no set of chart and I can do a hundred decks
78 cards
Standard smooth with a booklet. I'd have to do a booklet too. Maybe like just the
And maybe a primer night probably nicer book because I do have like a I'll probably maybe put a book out
She was something like that and then put a little I
Don't know it's gonna be a lot of work, but yeah, thank you person. That's the really cool
2000 yeah
I got this copy for $3 today
You have three heads. Yep. He's smart. You got a man. Do you have a male female and a male female?
Ha
I mean guys the only person that wants to come on is big otherwise
He's like he's the only person that wants to come on the show when they hate me in the show
He's the only one he I've kicked him off already twice tonight for being annoying and he's back again
What let's say let's say tell me
Hello, oh look at his face look at his face
Okay, do you guys see this are you guys seeing what I'm seeing? Do you see what I see?
Do you hear what I hear? I don't hear them. I'm deaf
Hold on
Stig hold on. I'm deaf. I'm I know you are hold on
Say have you seen this?
Stig do you know this woman right here?
Oh shit
Okay, you know this woman
And tell me who this is no, please identify the following person
I have never had any interactions with that woman in my life
Who is it who do you see? I
Haven't played a picture. I have never had interactions with that woman in my life
This one right here
No, no, no, this one. Oh, yeah
This one her who is that? Is that you in drag? I have never had an araxis
No, why do you look just like why do you look exactly like that woman? Why do you look exactly like her? Is that your mother?
Yeah, my mother is much more beautiful than thank you very much
Okay, well, that's really an unfortunate thing to hear you say, but I'm here
I'm saying it looks like it looks like you it looks like I'm not gonna be racist or anything. Yeah
Yeah, I'll take good thing there. I don't know you're smiling
How about this one? Do you look like this? You're just making yourself look bad in all honesty. I am like racist
I'm throwing you a bone by saying that no nothing about race. You just look bad. I
Look bad. Why why I look bad in this it was like racist
Oh, I say who is this person? Oh, you were there my feelings
Say you know this person
Say this is true that this is a photo of you
Is that your is that your photo?
I've been I've also been raped. I don't know that around just like you've been because oh
My god
What is he talking about
Oh
We say I don't know that's enough that's enough third time
Oh, what a weirdo
What do I keep letting him back on guys tell me to stop
Insane Yokozuma. Yeah, I mean
I was trying to be like have a little bit of levity and like you know kind of a laugh a little bit and he gets all
But hurt. What the hell?
Hey, he's back guys, well, it will never end. It will never
Like if you guys whoever someone wants to dig back on
I need three votes. I need three people to type the number one in the chat right now. If you want, I'm back on. I'll head back on.
He said the R. He said the R word. I didn't like that.
Nice. I'll put my new glasses here, by the way, guys.
I don't like the word. I don't like the word. And plus it's not like...
YouTube doesn't like disrespect to me and other content creators, especially by rumble people. YouTube gets mad and then I don't want to get
troubled
Okay, one we have one one guys we need two more ones and then I'll sit I'll sit back up
He's not even backstage anymore, but I will I'll keep my word. Oh
Guys, I'm gonna let some instant
They've got this brand new instance. It's a really good it's called witches brew
Okay, two unreadable says two.
This is called witch's brew.
I got your incense.
It says, an rolled masala incense stick made in India.
Smells, smells so good.
Smells so good.
Let him back up yo.
So we only have one vote though.
And I have 18 people in the chat and only one person.
That's Jim said yes and everybody else said no.
Okay, I'm not being unfair you have one we have one yes one no so far nobody else has even bothered to go
This is cool guys, I love the incense right there. You just put it out like that. Ooh smoky
You don't want to see a fat water. Oh, yeah. Well, it's like you know, we don't have to be I love Guatemalan people
I love you know people from everywhere, but not to do with Guatemalan. It's just you with being an asshole
You're a legend around these chats. Okay. Well
You need to impress me a little bit more Jim and then maybe I'll consider
Bring me back up
Yeah, are you Joker? He said he will porn bomb me. Okay, I'm not gonna
He I mean he has before to and he's also and Q just did that to you form on me. I
Can't take it anymore
Yeah, I'm not gonna put up with it anymore see
Dance
You're not joker, okay, you look like jokers picture though
The picture with a joker here or look like yeah, we're not like Joe or mr. Big Pops a little bit, too
Mr.. Big Pops actually sent me a video like on Instagram I thought
SIG number two is
Because I'm not reading the chat either. I'm like I'm being honest. I'm not reading yet. I'm just
You honestly got enough ones. I would put them in
If the chat does not even care enough to put type the number one
Except for Jim
It says something and then and people do have the energy to put number two
Nancy and coming through this one
Literally oh
Wow, okay
So at least it's been off this week. That's why I was wondering like where's Lisa. Yeah, she's been off this week
Not crazy
If you see her on this I'm just for a little bit
There are two to two
The crowd is spoken
Sorry sick. I mean I try to be fair, right?
I'm like, I don't want you on but if it's somebody else says they're willing and how guys somebody else wants them on
Someone donates $10 to the cash up. I'll put it back on
Otherwise, I'm not gonna deal with them anymore
Or you can or donate 25 I'll kick them off for the 24 hours, but yeah, it's two two twos in the chat. We have twos in the chat
Okay
Let me see what's going on with my TikTok.
He strikes you out, yeah.
So the TikTok, okay, TikTok is going really, really well,
guys, because I'm able to,
I'm able to,
Do my readings on it like like long readings and it's like I have fun doing it
And it's like and people when I like just do questions on there
I think I don't really just I like it like here too like where it's like, you know, we never know what that happens
I do like be able to do my
My member readings too. Okay, so
You see so tiktok gives away like all this like money to like you think it's not real money
But look there's like this little bear game
And you just like put like little gems in the basket and then it gives you like 25 cents or something
You see every game. Hold on. Yeah, see these little bear until there's like two cents and you just put you like this
You know just like that. It's like really easy and then you go
Share and then you know I like my share
I just like to send video like I'll pop people link and then I just close it and then it yeah, and I got it
Up there it goes. I just made like eight cents. Okay, I
Filled in things in the pan. I go like this and I collect them all
What does it say?
14 cents. I just made 14 cents. Talk about money you guys. I just made 14 cents now look how much I have I have I
Have 59 cents I
Can use that 59 cents to probably give a bunch of hot guys gifts
Anyway, so
Made eight cents. There was actually 15 cents now
I have a 59 cent balance, but I have to have a dollar before I can take out anything so
Almost there guys though
Pretty funny, this is how yeah, we'll train us to feed the machine. Well, I
Mean train me playing farm build in 20 years ago. I'm trained
Okay
Okay.
Ooh, okay.
And look, here's my,
here's me on TikTok, you wanna see me on TikTok?
See, look at the fast one going.
Doing a reading. What does it say on the screen? It says highlight of the life. Thanks for enjoying. You see it makes these little automatic like things
That's one of them
They look a little heartly thing. Hello. Hello. He's like love it. It's gonna love being thrown. I love it. I love it
Is that the only one I have? Yeah
Okay
So now I'm gonna look at
What is my clock?
1710 is that the time 510. Yeah, so what does this mean?
So this is Monday August 4th, right
It says sun rose at 608 a.m. We'll set at
19 was 19
745 p.m
Sun is in 1241 Leo in the seventh house
conjunct with Mercury
It is a 32nd week of the year too
So I don't know there's a clock, you know the Internet is a does zodiac has a clock, right?
We live in time. So right here. This clock strikes 13
Labyrinth has been solved
I'm to talk famous now
Not really. I have like I have almost a thousand followers. I'll take talk. I do get
Maybe a hundred fifty two hundred people coming through the chat maybe like ten fifteen people in the chat
This has been there for a couple weeks
I'm already monetized with the membership.
That's pretty good, I think.
An illusion?
Well, what isn't an illusion on this planet?
Most stuff is illusory.
The material is just pure matter.
It's pure dark matter.
Makes with some light, right?
I'll read some more, yeah, I'll read some more, uh, Faust. Okay. Hold on.
Like that.
Okay. Faust.
You guys want to hear more? I'll read some more.
Okay. This says,
Says freelude on the stage manager dramatic poet jester. Okay, so that's the setup. It says
manager yee
To have so often stood by me in times of need and tribulation come say what hope in any German nation
For what we undertake have ye I have much to die
I much desire to give proud a pleasure a proud pleasure because they live and let us live
The posts, the boards are up, and here at Leisure, the crowd expects a feast in what we'll give.
Those sitting now with eyebrows raised quite calmly there would be gladly be amazed.
I know how one makes all minds akin, yet so embarrassed I have never been.
in truth accustomed to the best, they're not.
But they have read an awful, really awful lot.
How shall we plan that all be fresh and new
and with a meaning yet attractive too?
For I do like to see
Them crowding, urging, when toward our booth, the stream sets in a pace, and with his powerful, repeated surging, pours through the straight and narrow gait of grace, when still in broad daylight, air, it is for, ear, it is for, they fight and push their way up to the wicket, and as the famines stricken at the baker's door, they nearly break their necks to get a ticket.
This miracle upon says a very folk the poet alone can work today my friend oh show it
Poet I beg you of that motley crowd cease telling at sight of whom the spirit takes to flight
Inveil from me the billowing mass, compelling, us to his vortex with resistless might.
No, leave me to the tranquil heavenly dwelling, where only blooms for poets pure delight,
where love and friendship give the heart their blessings, with God-like hand creating and progressing.
Ah, all that from the bosom's depth spring-flowing, all that from shy and stammering lifts his past.
sometimes success and sometimes failure knowing, to each wild moment's power a praise casts.
Offed only after years in credit glowing, doth it appear in perfect form at last.
What gleams is born, but for the moment's pages, the true remains.
Unlossed to after-ages, jester, could I but hear no more of after-ages.
Suppose the thought of them, my mind engages.
Who'd give the present world its fun?
That will it have an ought to have its too.
The presence of the gallant chap revealed to you, I think, is also worth while being shown,
who pleasantly, can just himself in part, is not embittered by the people's whim.
He likes to have a crowd surrounding him, more certainly to stir and thrill each heart.
So do be good, show you can set the fusion, let fantasy be heard, with all her chorus,
sense, reason, sentiment, and passion.
Manager, but more than all, do let enough occur.
Men come to look to see they most prefer.
If as they gaze, much is reeled off and spun,
so that the subtle crowd gaves all it can a multitude.
You will have won at once won, you then will be a much loved man.
You can compel the mass by mass alone.
Each in the end will seek out something as his own.
Bring much and you'll bring this or that to everyone and each will leave contented when the play is done
If you give out a piece give it at once in pieces rag out like this your fame increases
Easy to stage so easy to invent
What uses this a whole fashion and presents?
The public still will pick it all to pieces.
Poet, you do not feel how bad such handy work must be.
How little that becomes the artist's true.
I see, neat, gentlemanly botchery is now a sovereign rule with you.
Manager reproof, like this leaves me quite unoffended, a man who does his work effectively
intended, must stick to tools that are best for it, reflect you have a tender wood to
split, and those for whom you write just see, if this one's driven by hither by NUE.
Another leaves in the book a banquet seated with his vapors, and what's the very worst
will always be many come fresh from reading magazines and papers.
Men haste distraught to us as to the masquerade, and every step but winged by curiosity the
ladies give a treat, all their best to raid, and play their part without a fee.
Why do you dream in lofty poet land? Why does the full house make you gay?
Observe the patrons near at hand. They are half cold. Half course. Are they?
One when the play is over hopes the game of cards a wild night on a winches breasts and other shoes
Why then with such aim?
Poor silly bars will you torment so much the gracious muses give only more and ever ever more I say
Then, from the goal, you nevermore can stray.
Seek to be wilder men, that is my view, but satisfy them?
That is hard to do.
Who is attacking you, pain or delight?
Poet, go hence, and seek yourself another slave.
What, shall the poet take the highest right, the right of man, that right which nature
gave, and wantonly, for your sake, trifle it away?
How doth he ever—how doth he over every heart hold sway?
A element in slave, it is not the harmony that from his breath starts, then winds the
world in turn back in all his heart.
When nature forces lengths and thread and ending, and careless whirling on the spindle
round, when all lies inharmonic throngs unblending in sill and harsh, confusion sound, who parts
the changeless theories of creation?
that each enliven moves in rhythmic time,
who summons each enjoying the general ordination,
in consecrated noble harmonies to chime,
who bids the storm with raging passions lower,
the sunset with a solemn mourning glow, meaning glow,
who scatters springtime's every lovely flower
along the pathway where his love may go.
Who twines the verdant leaves unmeaning slighted into a wreath of honor
Mead of every field who makes a limp is sure the gods united that power of man the poet has revealed
Jester then use those handsome powers as your aid and carry on this poet trade
Okay
As one a love adventure carries, by chance, one nears, one feels, one tarries.
And bit by bit, one gets into a tangle.
This grows, then comes a tiff, a wrangle.
One is enwrapped, now one sees pain advance, an air, one is aware, it is a real romance.
So let us also, such a drama, give.
Each lives it, though it's known to few, and grasp it where you will, there's interest for you, in motley pictures with a little clarity, much air, and a spike of verity.
Thus can be the best of drinks be brewed to cheer and edify the multitude.
Youth's fairs bloom collects its expectation before your play and harks the revelation.
Each tender soul intent absorbs a melancholy nourishment, then now one thought and now another thought you start, each sees what he has carried in his heart.
As yet they are unprepared for weeping and for laughter. They still revere the fight.
illusion they adore. A mind once formed finds not, made right thereafter. A growing mind
will thank you ever more. Poet, then give me back the time of growing, when I myself
was growing too, when crowding songs, a fountain flowing, just forth unceasing, ever new, when
still the mist
By world revealing, the bud is miracle bespoke, when I the thousand blossoms broke profusely
through the valley's trailing, not yet enough had I win budding youth, joys and allusion
yearning toward the truth.
Give impulse, it's unfettered dower, the bliss so deep, it is full of pain, the strength of hate loves mighty power.
Oh, give me back my youth again.
Jester, youth, my good friend, you need most in the fight when enemies come on, heart-pressing.
When clinging to your neck so tight, the dearest maidens hang caressing, when from afar a wreath
entrances, luring to hard one goal the runner's might, when after madly whirling dances a man,
carousing, drinks away the night. But on the lyre's familiar strings to play with grace and spirit
ever, and sweep with lovely wanderings toward goals, you choose for your endeavor.
And that is your duty, Agents Serves, and we revere you for it no less dearly.
Age makes not childish, as one oft avares, it finds us still true children merely.
Manager words have been entertained enough, let me at last see action too, while compliments
your turning idle stuff.
Some useful thing might come to view.
Why talk of wanting for the mood?
If you pretend your poet's good, command then poet's poetry.
What we're in need of, that full well you know, you want to sip strong drink and go start the brew without delay.
Never is done tomorrow, what is not done today.
And one should not, one should let no day slip by with resolution seek, seize the possible straight away,
by forelock and with quick contagious trust.
Then holding fast, you will not let it further fly and you will labor on because you must.
Upon our German stage, you are aware.
East tries out what you wish to display.
So, in your work for me, today's scenes,
mechanism, you are not to spare.
Use both the lights of heaven, great and small.
The stars above are yours to squander.
Nor water fire, nor rocky wall, nor beast, nor birds,
are lacking yonder.
Thus, in our narrow house of boards,
preside and on through all creation's circle stride
and wander on the speed considered wealth.
from heaven through the world to hell.
How was that?
Did you like that?
Hi, you love the reading?
Okay, good.
I hope you did like that.
That is, he was addressing his three people
in his kingdom or his household.
I think they were the manager, the poet, and the jester.
And each of them has their purpose in his house,
He basically saying hey, it's a show and everyone's just you're not fun, right? I
kind of did relate to that so
Anyway, I do have my new glasses coming. I cannot wait to show you my new glasses. They are colorful
They are interesting. They are
It was they were a good deal three for ten dollars so other stuff coming too, but I
Will show you the glasses then I might take a little break for a while. It's 524. We'll see what happens tonight
Just having a nice
Cool night. I didn't help you enjoyed that the fast though. I'm really gonna read you that whole thing eventually, right?
So I have my make last of theirs a few stops away from the house now
Hi KZ, how are you?
So I don't know, it's been quiet sometimes.
If you guys do are interested in like, you know,
at least even if not having a private reading,
if you guys want to go over to the TikTok sometimes,
it is kind of like fun.
And I've had a few people from this chat go over there.
I've had a few people from there come over here.
It's a good way to promote everything.
They are different kind of shows.
And so, okay, I didn't saw, okay, that's fine.
Shit, take out some of this stuff.
Okay, that's better.
Where's my stuff order?
Track my orders.
How many stops away?
Hey, Psychic, can you unblock your ZKZ account?
Sure, I will
Okay, so John
Okay, back my orders
Okay, I read between 415 715 is now
How far
One stop away. It's here. It's okay. Yeah, they're here. He's like at the house
that's pretty cool i have my new glasses i'm gonna yeah i can block your account let me see if i can
i have some uh some reading glasses reading glasses so streaming um let me see uh studio youtube.com
i'll have a look at the block list
Hold on, what is this happening here?
Someone said, I think that people
that have a membership, wouldn't you say?
What does this person say?
I probably agree with them.
Channel comments, view more, let me see.
I said, I don't know, I think that people
have a membership to have a free reading,
it's just a suggestion, that's all.
Yeah, I'll say members.
Members will have received at least an extra 15 minutes in paid readings in the private, I'll say private.
Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you, Halo, for commenting.
So let me look in the ban list.
We'll see if I see KV Community Moderation.
Let's see, if I see KV here.
No, no, no.
Okay, I'll pick up this person.
Hmm
I'll take some people off the off the list. I don't know everybody though amber
Okay CB got you
Okay, I don't know this later. Oh, there's there's you me
How do you meet?
We're real.
Okay, I think that I got most of the people.
Do I see KZ?
Okay, I'll take this person off the list.
Okay, I think I got KZ, can I dry?
Okay, Vicky, okay.
Okay, guys, I take a lot of people off the list, so go ahead and test now. Okay, I saved it.
Oh, yeah, and I did, yeah, it was my community board, so that should go on to everybody. That's just the numbers, okay?
Okay guys, I am banned. I am banned people. Yeah, there you go
Let me see I think my things are here
Mean he was right there. I'm the next stop. Okay. I'm the next stop, okay. Oh
My gosh, my cat is like destroyed this freaking cord. Oh
fix
My little naughty cat
Just a little naughty guy
That works better
Guys if you want to check out my
My store as well, I have like a little influencer thing.
It just will take you to Amazon.
It'll just show you the products
that I bought on Amazon and recommend.
Let's get a link.
Here's a copy.
Guys, you wanna have a look at it?
It's right here.
Check out this link.
Okay, yeah, everyone subscribe to KZ.
Okay, but yeah, check out this Amazon link right there. It's my little
Influencer store. Oh
Tommy James. How about Tommy James? Like you go fuck yourself. How about that? Okay?
Hey, let me have a safe here. How about you go fuck yourself Tommy James?
Okay, here's what I got guys. Oh, wow. Hold on. Okay
These were I think these are my favorite. I'm gonna be these ones right here
Tell me how these look on me
How are those?
I don't like them. Kind of like greenish. I like them. Do you like them?
Many people are in chat. They're different. Uh-oh, that's not a good sign. Things are different. I mean, I think they look good.
I like this table. You're cool. Oh, I have a few more. That's that one. I have the black one. Maybe the black one
These are cool
Little bit stream like that. I like how big bull they are. They're very bulls and look at butterflies a little bit
Okay, what else do we have that color? These are just 10 bucks with repairs and
You know, I don't have to go on right now, they're not
Here's the third color I have it's kind of like a tan
I like these ones too, they're kind of like the red
Okay. Well, at least I have some more stuff. I have some more colors and stuff. There we go. I do like them.
They're nice
powerful looking glasses. Okay.
Anyway, I'm Tommy James. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to like, you know, you're being really good.
I get kind of like yours here, and you keep telling me that when it's raw, it's...
You have a high, yeah.
Hey, don't worry about what people call me, and we'll worry about yourself, okay?
Okay? Capiche?
Capiche?
Okay.
Everyone just be worried about themselves.
There we go.
I mean, it's true, like there are some people that are in this in the metaphysical that will do pulled readings and stuff like that
I'm very genuine with what I do. I'm not trying to like blow smoke of anybody's ass
I'm just genuine and I've had really really good reviews from my readings and so people that will keep saying is a bullshit
That's not true. And it's like this lander is actually I've never scammed a person in my life, right?
never
Or what I I'm not I don't I don't scam people. I've been scammed, but I don't scam people, right?
I'm honest. I've never, I'll basically make it, I'll make, uh, I'll satisfy people. I'll make
people happy. You know, I'll, I'll, I'll give you back whatever energy. I like to exchange energy,
you know, give back good energy too. Okay. I think I really do like these glasses though. Okay.
Okay.
How are we doing guys?
Tricks is all in bit in this core than half in these core, you know cats will always be a little bit destroyers. You like I'm okay good
I'll just I'll put on these. Oh, yeah, I like the black ones. I like these black ones
And you have to look a little bit closer because they do throw like their readers, right?
I don't know if they have the blue blocker right now
They're basically it's an Oprah. Where's this kind of glasses? I'd be like Oprah also
They're like kind of oversized I just like them
Okay, so you're yeah the Amazon link that is my influencer store
And so yes, I you know those are all products that I've bought like there's a section on the tarot
There's a section on technology
This I'm not afraid. I think there's some of them. I saw a couple a couple of products on there
but I bought all the products I own and
That's my Amazon store. I would got accepted into the influencer program also as an affiliate as an associate Amazon associate
Pretty cool
Yeah, and you can probably apply to you if you just go Amazon influencer apply and then you can just plug in one of your accounts
And if you're like, yeah, I think if they consider you're an influencer, they will approve you
But I got I do have a background in internet marketing and stuff like that
So just realized like I do kind of know what I've been doing kind of like internet marketing since like 2012
So maybe this little clue is so why I'm I also have a marketing degree. I'm my bachelor's in marketing
I think marketing is a great great field, but it is
It is about monetization, you know, and so
There'll be all kinds of unflattering kind of stuff said about it, too
But as you when you market you make a you'll basically make a mark
Which is like you know aiming you're in your aiming to sell to sell right?
It's just a basic basic supply and demand, right?
Do they have the labyrinth hero I did I put that up there? I think I did I think I have that in the
Yeah, they had the labyrinth hero in there. I
Think I did add that. Let me have a look at my Amazon store
If they have my Amazon here, so let me see, Influencer.
I can actually add videos and stuff to it too,
so guys, you're gonna just take search
for Amazon Influencer, it'll take you
to this Influencer program.
Well, let me see, Influencer.
Okay. Amazon. Okay.
So I go connect it. Okay. Okay. Now it's ready. Okay. So this is my shop.
And you can see, oh, there's the, has idealists. Okay. And so these will say tarot. Okay. So this
is like the tarot section. And so this has like my, there's a slot that I use. Oh, and that's
It's a lot of the books I have.
And let me see if my labyrinth is there.
Labyrinth is, yes, it's right here.
So if you'd like to purchase that labyrinth deck,
there it is right there, see?
There's all, and I have all these decks.
I have all these decks.
And these are ones I recommend,
but I really do recommend the gold leaf writer weight
or just a regular writer weight to learn.
But these are also books I have and stuff.
I have a lot of terrible stuff, okay?
Okay.
I hope you guys will have a look at some of the stuff.
And yeah, I do, I would like to actually, you know,
have people, you know, check out some of my recommendations.
I do really highly recommend those things.
Okay, it's a piece.
Yeah.
Pretty cool though.
Yeah, so I'm really working hard on,
Okay, I'm gonna say success here guys two and a half hours. Okay. I'll send them for like three hours right now
And then I might come on later. All right, and I will come on later
For sure. It just seems like a little bit quiet. There's 10 people
No, I'm just gonna end now because there's 10 people, but I'll be back. Okay. I'll be back probably 8 p.m. I'll see you guys soon